<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Homepage</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 13:32:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruby&#39;s Deluxe</title>
      <link>/post/rubys-deluxe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 13:32:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/rubys-deluxe/</guid>
      <description>On our way to Astoria, my wife and I stopped for lunch in Seaside. Our first choice was a fish &amp;amp; chips place we&amp;rsquo;d heard about that turned out to be closed, so we went down the street a block to Ruby&amp;rsquo;s instead, which turned out to be an excellect decision.
The burger I got was the Ruby&amp;rsquo;s Deluxe (with cheese), which is on paper is a very, very standard burger:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Deluxe</title>
      <link>/post/super-deluxe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 19:43:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/super-deluxe/</guid>
      <description>Today we finally went to Super Deluxe, Portland&amp;rsquo;s newest soon-to-be-a-chain burger joint, where I witnessed a double murder. The victim? The In-N-Out restaurant chain, but also the Burger King across the street. The Super Deluxe (both burger and restaurant are so named) is the Platonic Form of the fast food diner burger. Not a fancy thing with goat cheese and bacon jam, but similar to its drive-thru cousins only in the loosest sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Rye</title>
      <link>/post/turkey-rye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 09:25:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/turkey-rye/</guid>
      <description>My first post-burger-week post!
Burger Week was a worthwhile endeavor, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t cheap. So this week, isntead of eating lunch out I went down the street to the grocery store and bought the following items:
 Marble rye bread Deli sliced turkey (peppered and and herb-garlic) Some kind of microgreens (maybe peas? I can&amp;rsquo;t recall) Horseradish Sriracha mayo Honey champagne mustard &amp;ldquo;Old Croc&amp;rdquo; extra sharp cheddar (it&amp;rsquo;s too sharp to slice properly: it just crumbles)  And every day for lunch in ~5-10 minutes I made the delicious sandwich you see here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Black and Blue</title>
      <link>/post/oregon-black-and-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 19:00:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/oregon-black-and-blue/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m assuming it takes an hour to make this burger, because that&amp;rsquo;s how long we had to wait once we&amp;rsquo;d ordered. If so, then not a minute was wasted: Bar Maven&amp;rsquo;s Oregon Black and Blue, my 11th and final burger of #portlandburgerweek, was delicious. Nice, thick patty with perfectly powerful cheese on a bun that was just good enough not to distract from the rest of the meal. If I had a complaint, it would be that that I didn&amp;rsquo;t get much of marionberry spread, which I was pretty excited about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cornholio</title>
      <link>/post/cornholio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 15:38:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cornholio/</guid>
      <description>The Burnside Brewing Cornholio had the unintended honor of being #portlandburgerweek burger number 10. A solid but unexceptional meal, save for the incredible jalapeno cream cheese. Was it just jalapenos and cream cheese, or something more complex? Whatever it was made of the combination was delicious, and it convinced some of the other mediocre ingredients (slightly stale chicharrón, not really roasted corn, bland bun) to come together into a pretty decent burger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buckaroo Burger</title>
      <link>/post/buckaroo-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 22:10:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/buckaroo-burger/</guid>
      <description>Burger number 9 in #portlandburgerweek is the Buckaroo Burger at Double Barrel Tavern. As usual the Double Barrel is on top of their business and getting a burger was a quick, painless process. The burger itself was a highlight of the week, and the patty itself may have been the best cooked that I&amp;rsquo;ve had so far, but overall it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a top contender. The BBQ sauce was great, but the burger felt like it needed something—maybe carrots?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fat Brando</title>
      <link>/post/the-fat-brando/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 14:54:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-fat-brando/</guid>
      <description>The number 8 burger for this year&amp;rsquo;s #portlandburgerweek is the Fat Brando from Home: A Bar, and for the second year in a row they took something that sounds nasty and made it delicious. The Fat Brando isn&amp;rsquo;t the same triumph that last year&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Picnic&amp;rdquo; burger was (it ends up being a favorite for both me and Marina), but it&amp;rsquo;s a tasty balance of flavors and not the horrifying grease pile (the horror&amp;hellip;the horror&amp;hellip;) it looks like in the official photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Mike</title>
      <link>/post/big-mike/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 18:08:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/big-mike/</guid>
      <description>#portlandburgerweek burger number 7 was the Big Mike at EastBurn Public House. The sauce was excellent (and deliciously mustard-y), but could have been applied more liberally, and the fried pickles were great, when I found them. Overall a good burger kept from greatness by conservative application of ingredients (and some not great lettuce). EastBurn is a well-oiled machine, though: I came in at 5:45pm and had my burger inside of 15 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piggy Walls</title>
      <link>/post/piggy-walls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 21:23:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/piggy-walls/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a two-burger night, my friends! Say hello to the Piggy Walls from Tilt, burger number 6 in this year&amp;rsquo;s #portlandburgerweek. This thing is a behemoth. The second patty is arguably unnecessary. Even my tremendous maw could barely fight around it. Marina had to spend a few seconds psyching herself up and getting in a few deep breaths before trying to take a bite. But that bite is worth it! This is one delicious burger, just don&amp;rsquo;t expect to eat anything else: lifting it up is a workout and it sounds like an encyclopedia when it hits the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nacho Burger</title>
      <link>/post/nacho-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 21:13:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nacho-burger/</guid>
      <description>Burger number 5 in this year&amp;rsquo;s #portlandburgerweek, the Nacho Burger at the Bit House Saloon. We arrived at the right time: we watched the line grow to fill the front of the bar as we ate our burgers. The burger itself was excellent: great balance of flavors with spicy sauce I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to like as much as I did&amp;ndash;they pour a bunch on so you can mop up the excess with your burger, which may not sound appetizing, but was delightful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haole Burger</title>
      <link>/post/haole-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 19:43:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/haole-burger/</guid>
      <description>Burger number 4 in #portlandburgerweek is the Haole Burger at Alameda Brewing Company, and it is accurately named&amp;ndash;perhaps too accurately. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get any identifiable &amp;ldquo;island&amp;rdquo; flavor: instead I mostly just got the taste of the mainland&amp;ndash;mayonnaise and salt. If you love spam, give it a shot, but not my favorite burger so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spicy Pork Burger</title>
      <link>/post/spicy-pork-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 13:09:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/spicy-pork-burger/</guid>
      <description>#portlandburgerweek burger number 3, Danwei Canting&amp;rsquo;s Spicy Pork Burger is a petite little item, almost more of a slider than a burger. It&amp;rsquo;s good, but could definitely be a lot spicier. Tasty thai tea, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grappler</title>
      <link>/post/the-grappler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 21:41:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-grappler/</guid>
      <description>Second burger of #portlandburgerweek, but (currently) number one in my heart, this is The Grappler from the Lay Low Tavern. Awesome blend of sweet (apples!) and savory (gorgonzola! beef!). Eat it fast: it&amp;rsquo;s best hot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pulled Pork Torta</title>
      <link>/post/pulled-pork-torta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 15:15:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pulled-pork-torta/</guid>
      <description>First burger of #portlandburgerweek, the Pulled Pork Torta at the Smokehouse Tavern. Pretty good! Pulled pork is a high-risk food that can either be delicious and flavorful or a disgusting mound of damp, soggy meat. This was, thankfully, the former. Not entirely sure what made it a torta, though.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>